Are you the exception... or are you the rule?
He's Just Not That Into You is a comedy, romance,
drama film directed by Ken Kwapis.
Have you ever sat by the phone wondering why he said he would call, but didn't, or you can't figure out why she
doesn't want to sleep with you anymore, or why your relationship just isn't going to the next level...
they're just not that into you.
Gigi just wants a man who says he'll call—and does—while
Alex advises her to stop waiting by the phone.
Beth wants a proposal after years of a committed relationship with her
boyfriend, Neil, who sees nothing  wrong with the status quo.
Janine's not sure if she can trust her husband, Ben, who
can't quite trust himself around Anna.
Anna can't decide between the sexy married guy, or her straightforward, no-sparks
standby, Conor, who can't get over the fact that he can't have her.
And Mary, who's found an entire network of loving, supportive
men, just needs to find one who's straight.
Gigi Phillips, played by Ginnifer Goodwin.
Alex, played by Justin Long.
Beth Murphy, played by Jennifer Aniston.
Neil, played by Ben Affleck.
Janine Gunders, played by Jennifer Connelly.
Ben Gunders, played by Bradley Cooper.
He's Just Not That into You is a 2009 American-German romantic comedy-drama film directed by Ken
Kwapis, based on Greg Behrendt and Liz Tuccillo's 2004 self-help book of the same name.
It follows nine people and their varying romantic problems.
Gigi, a common thread amongst the characters, is followed more closely than the other eight and has a more
developed storyline as she consistently misreads all of her romantic partners' behaviors.
She meets Alex, who helps her to interpret signs given to her by her dates.
The film stars an ensemble cast of Ben Affleck, Jennifer Aniston, Drew Barrymore, Jennifer Connelly,
Kevin Connolly, Bradley Cooper, Ginnifer Goodwin, Scarlett Johansson, and Justin Long.
The film was produced by New Line Cinema and Flower Films, the production company
owned by Barrymore, who is also the film's executive producer.
Production began in Baltimore in 2007.
The film was released on February 6, 2009, by Warner Bros.
Pictures to mixed reviews.
It grossed $27.7 million on its opening weekend
and over $178.8 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of friendship, based on novel or book,
married couple, relationship problems, relationship.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.